{"lang": "da", "name": "dacy_test_trf_no_test", "version": "0.1.0", "description": "\n    <a href=\"https://github.com/centre-for-humanities-computing/Dacy\"><img src=\"https://centre-for-humanities-computing.github.io/DaCy/_static/icon.png\" width=\"175\" height=\"175\" align=\"right\" /></a>\n\n    # DaCy test transformer\n\n    DaCy is a Danish language processing framework with state-of-the-art pipelines as well as functionality for analysing Danish pipelines.\n    DaCy's largest pipeline has achieved State-of-the-Art performance on Named entity recognition, part-of-speech tagging and dependency \n    parsing for Danish on the DaNE dataset. At the time of publishment it also encorporates the only models for fine-grained NER using the 18 annotation types from Ontonotes.\n    Check out the [DaCy repository](https://github.com/centre-for-humanities-computing/DaCy) for material on how to use DaCy and reproduce the results. \n    DaCy also contains guides on usage of the package as well as behavioural test for biases and robustness of Danish NLP pipelines.\n    ", "author": "Centre for Humanities Computing Aarhus", "email": "Kenneth.enevoldsen@cas.au.dk", "url": "https://chcaa.io/#/", "license": "Apache-2.0 License", "spacy_version": ">=3.5.0,<3.6.0", "spacy_git_version": "dec81508d", "vectors": {"width": 0, "vectors": 0, "keys": 0, "name": null}, "labels": {"tok2vec": [], "ner": ["CARDINAL", "DATE", "EVENT", "FACILITY", "GPE", "LANGUAGE", "LAW", "LOCATION", "MONEY", "NORP", "ORDINAL", "ORGANIZATION", "PERCENT", "PERSON", "PRODUCT", "QUANTITY", "TIME", "WORK OF ART"]}, "pipeline": ["tok2vec", "ner"], "components": ["tok2vec", "ner"], "disabled": [], "performance": {"ents_f": 0.6730700818, "ents_p": 0.7199391172, "ents_r": 0.6319305277, "ents_per_type": {"PERSON": {"p": 0.5925925926, "r": 0.64, "f": 0.6153846154}, "NORP": {"p": 0.6818181818, "r": 0.612244898, "f": 0.6451612903}, "ORGANIZATION": {"p": 0.652027027, "r": 0.6476510067, "f": 0.6498316498}, "CARDINAL": {"p": 0.850678733, "r": 0.8318584071, "f": 0.841163311}, "GPE": {"p": 0.8145695364, "r": 0.6373056995, "f": 0.7151162791}, "DATE": {"p": 0.7861271676, "r": 0.8343558282, "f": 0.8095238095}, "LOCATION": {"p": 0.4230769231, "r": 0.4074074074, "f": 0.4150943396}, "FACILITY": {"p": 0.6, "r": 0.1428571429, "f": 0.2307692308}, "WORK OF ART": {"p": 0.6923076923, "r": 0.1956521739, "f": 0.3050847458}, "TIME": {"p": 0.5, "r": 0.4, "f": 0.4444444444}, "PRODUCT": {"p": 0.4137931034, "r": 0.3333333333, "f": 0.3692307692}, "MONEY": {"p": 0.9589041096, "r": 0.9210526316, "f": 0.9395973154}, "PERCENT": {"p": 0.9230769231, "r": 1.0, "f": 0.96}, "ORDINAL": {"p": 0.6, "r": 0.2727272727, "f": 0.375}, "QUANTITY": {"p": 0.7272727273, "r": 0.7272727273, "f": 0.7272727273}, "LANGUAGE": {"p": 0.5, "r": 0.0357142857, "f": 0.0666666667}, "LAW": {"p": 1.0, "r": 0.3888888889, "f": 0.56}, "EVENT": {"p": 0.5, "r": 0.0588235294, "f": 0.1052631579}}, "tok2vec_loss": 1108.6378405011, "ner_loss": 4269.0391463607}, "requirements": ["spacy-transformers>=1.0.3,<1.1.0"], "sources": [{"name": "DANSK - Danish Annotations for NLP Specific TasKs", "url": "", "license": "", "author": ""}, {"test": "test"}]}